truliantfcu.org 2006-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Truliant Federal Credit Union

Privacy Policy

 _The information in this policy statement reflects the continuation of how we have always safeguarded your personal privacy. If you have relationships elsewhere, we encourage you to thoroughly review their privacy practices for your information and protection.  
_  
 **How We're Protecting Your Privacy**

 **General Information  
** At Truliant Federal Credit Union and our service organization, Truliances, we are committed to safeguarding your privacy. That is why we have always held member information and transactions in the strictest of confidence, and have never sold member information for use by non-affiliated third parties. As explained below, we shall continue to uphold our commitment to protect information entrusted to us by our members. This notice describes how we protect the privacy of your personal information at the Credit Union and Truliances. Throughout this notice, the word "information" refers to personal information about you that may not be publicly available and the word "you" means Credit Union members or former members and customers of Truliant's.

 **Information That We Collect**   
We collect information about you from the following sources: 

  * Applications and other forms you submit to us. 
  * Information about your transactions with us. 
  * Information about your transactions with our affiliates. (i.e. Credit Union Auto Buying Service, etc.) 
  * Credit and other consumer reports. 

**Information We Disclose  
** Except for the situations described below, we do not disclose information that we collect about you. As a trusted financial partner, we are committed to providing you with competitive products and value-added services to meet your financial needs. This commitment to service excellence necessitates that on a limited basis, we may share all the information we collect, as referenced above, with our affiliated third party financial service provider, which provides investment, auto locator and insurance services. This includes, for example, the Credit Union Auto Buying Service and MEMBERS Financial Services program, which allow us to provide our members greater options and money-saving benefits. We may also disclose the information we collect, as referenced above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. For instance, this includes companies that assist us in printing, processing and mailing information (letters, postcards, etc.) that we provide you regarding new products and special offers. We may disclose information about you under other circumstances as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to follow your authorized instructions such as ordering checks, to conduct the operations of the Credit Union, or to protect the security of your financial records. To protect our members' privacy, you can be assured that we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide to the specific functions we ask them to perform.

 **How We Protect Your Information  
** We restrict access to information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your information. If you ever have questions about the use of your personal information, please call a Member Service Representative at your local number or 800-822-0382. If we make changes to this policy, we will give you the required notification.
